누가 종업원한테
롤러스케이트 신기쟀어?
Whose idea was it to put
everybody in the diner on skates?
어떤 웬수같은 손님이
건의함에 건의했대
Some idiot customer put a suggestion
in the suggestion box.
내 의견이 뽑혔구나!
-Oh, my God! They took my idea!
-That was you?
- 너였어?
- 응
Okay, there you go.
자, 간다
Rachel, I made you cocoa.
- 레이첼, 여기 코코아
- 안돼!
너무 고마... 안돼!
Oh, that's so....
Oh, my God! Are you guys okay?
괜찮니?
그림 좋고!
Oh, my.
The One With a Chick and a Duck
수염 기르니까
꼭 사탄 같다
You know, with that goatee,
you kind of look like Satan.
So that's why the priest
threw holy water on me.
그래서 신부가 나한테
성수를 뿌려댔군?
제발 기운 좀 내
You have to cheer up.
You should come out with Ross and me.
케이트 때문에
종일 징징 짜지만 말고
Anything is better than sitting
here crying all day about Kate.
같이 어울리자구
울었던 건... 아무도
퀸시 말을 안 믿잖아
I was crying because
nobody believed Quincy's theory.
- 안녕
- 왔냐?
I'm gonna be on TV!
나 TV 출연해!
- 정말?
- 그래
No way!
They're putting together a panel
to talk about the fossils in Peru.
페루에서 발견된
화석에 대해 말해달래
The Discovery Channel's filming it!
'디스커버리 채널'에 나와
이럴 수가!
Oh, my God!
Who's gonna watch that?
그걸 누가 본대?
- 고맙다, 갈까?
- 그래
Thanks. You ready to go?
I saw a girl with that vest.
그 조끼 여자도 입더라
고마워
Thanks.
Most of us think of chocolate and
baskets as traditional Easter gifts.
부활절 선물은 전통적으로
초콜릿 토끼나 바구니지만
Some people insist on
giving live chicks as presents.
병아리를 선물하는
이들도 있습니다
Unfortunately, most of these guys
won't live to see the 4th of July.
하지만 이 병아리들 대부분이
얼마 못 가 죽고 마는데
As a result of improper care,
they will be dead.
적절히 돌보지 못한
결과입니다
You guys got any of those baby chicks?
안녕하세요?
병아리 있죠?
I was watching this commercial on TV,
and, man, those things are cute!
TV 광고 보고 전화했는데
진짜 귀엽네요
안녕
피트, 돌아왔네요
이것 좀 보세요
Pete, you're back!
Hey, check this out!
스케이트네요!
Skates!
챈들러보단 힘 좋네요
아주 찌그러지더라구요
You're sturdier than Chandler.
He crumbled like a piece of paper.
How was your trip?
- 여행은 어땠어요?
- 자요
이게 뭐예요?
What'd you bring me?
일본 호텔 화장품!
Hotel toiletries from Japan!
대대손손 남길게요
These are gonna go
in my permanent collection.
-Want some coffee?
-That'd be great.
- 커피 드려요?
- 좋죠
Regular or decaf?
레귤러? 디카페인?
Whichever's closest.
- 가까운 걸로 줘요
- 네
-Ask me what I did today.
-What did you do today?
- 오늘 뭐했나 물어봐줘요
- 오늘 뭐했어요, 피트?
I bought a restaurant
and I'd like you to be the chef.
식당을 하나 샀는데
주방장이 돼줘요
네?
Can you believe he
offered me a restaurant?
식당을 맡으라는 게
믿어지니?
What a jerk.
You want me to kick his ass?
도둑놈!
뺨이라도 갈겨줄까?
하지만 그건
장난감 오븐 갖고
It's been my dream since
I got my first Easy-Bake Oven...
'모니카 빵집' 열 때부터
내 꿈이었어
...and opened Easy-Monica's Bakery.
죽도록 하고 싶고 자신 있어
고생도 할만큼 했다구
I would kill for this job.
I can totally do this job...
...and God knows, I've paid my dues.
But Pete's doing this
because he has a crush on me.
문제는 피트가
날 좋아한단 거야
And you're still not
attracted to him at all?
- 넌 전혀 관심 없고?
- 그래
How could I accept a restaurant
from him? I can't.
어떻게 식당을 덥석 받아?
난 못해
I couldn't accept a necklace
from Stu Vincent in the 7th grade.
7학년 때 빈센트가 준
목걸이도 안 받았다구
그건 다르지
그 사람은 양호 교사였잖아
But, Mon, that was totally different.
He was your health teacher.
됐어!
What, honey?
왜 그래?
어제 부딪히고 아직도
옆구리가 아파
My side hurts from when
you crashed into me.
정말 미안해
Oh, God, I'm so sorry.
- 괜찮...
- 맙소사!
Oh, God!
Hey, you guys. Guess what?
할 말 있어
요즘 웨이터도 해?
Got a job on a riverboat?
I didn't wear this suit for a year,
because you hated it.
네가 이 옷 싫어해서 1년 간
못 입었지만 헤어진 마당에...
You're not my girlfriend
anymore, so....
- 그 옷 보면 확실해지겠네
- 맞아
I see. This suit is making a point.
Now that you're on your own, you're
free to look as stupid as you'd like.
좋아, 이젠 맘껏
촌스럽게 하고 다녀
You like it, right?
- 넌 맘에 들지?
- 물론이지
I like it even more on you
than I did on Colonel Sanders.
KFC 할아버지보다
훨씬 멋져
오빠, 농담이야
할 말 있다며?
Ross, I'm kidding. Come here.
What were you gonna tell us?
11가지 양념엔
뭐뭐 들어가?
Was it how you
invented the cotton gin?
간다
롤러스케이트 건의한 지
얼마 만에 뽑혔어?
So after you put the suggestion
in the box...
...how long did it take
for it to happen?
한 3달쯤
About three months.
So I guess that's about two weeks
before the topless thing kicks in.
그럼 토플리스는
2주면 떡을 치겠군
- 얘들아
- 너냐?
I got you something.
Open it! Open it!
기대하시라!
얼른 열어봐
좋아
It's a chicken.
뼝아리네?
It's cute, huh?
귀엽지?
병아리에 대해서
뭐 알아?
You guys? Do you know
anything about chicks?
Fowl? No.
닭도 아니고
Women? No.
영계도 아니지
They are a huge responsibility.
기르기 얼마나 까다롭다구
특히 어릴 땐 더해
Especially at this age.
They require constant care.
They need just the right food
and lots and lots of love.
모이도 잘 주고
사랑을 쏟아 부어야 돼
그건 걱정 마
Well, no problem there.
Easy, Lenny.
적당히 하셔
So, I mean, have you thought about it?
생각해봤어요?
Okay, here's the thing.
그게 말이죠...
난 '그게'가 정말 싫어요
'그게' 왜요?
Not "the thing."
I hate "the thing."
What's "the thing"?
못하겠어요, 죄송해요
하고는 싶은데...
I can't do it.
I'm sorry. I wish I could...
... but you have these feelings for me.
부담 돼서 그래요
그것 때문이었어요?
그 문제라면 걱정 말아요
That's what you're worried about?
If that's the problem,
we've got no problem.
네?
얘기하려고 했는데
여행 중에 여잘 만났어요
I was gonna tell you over dinner,
but I met somebody else, on my trip.
이름은 앤, 기자이고
비행기에서 만났죠
Her name's Ann. She's a journalist.
We met on the plane.
땅콩 달라는 걸 땅굴 달라는
줄 알고 한바탕 웃었죠
She wanted to finish off
my peanuts.
I thought she said something else.
We had a big laugh.
- 오래 기다리기 싫어요
- 잘 됐어요
I got tired of waiting.
That's great. I'm sorry,
but I'm so happy for you.
이런 말 뭣하지만
정말 기뻐요
-Now I can work for you!
-I guess you can.
- 일할게요
- 그럴 줄 알았어요
Oh, my God! This is incredible!
세상에!
안 믿어져요
You know what? I'm gonna roll
right into that office and quit!
당장 굴러가서
사표 낼래요
All right!
그래요
- 좀 밀어줄래요?
- 네
Could you give me a little push?
Good luck!
- 잘 해요
- 나 관둔다!
I'm quitting!
I'm okay! I'm all right!
저 멀쩡해요
That's exciting.
You went to Japan, made up a woman.
일본 갈 때 만난 여자라...
멋진데요
네?
What?
그 여자...
지어낸 거죠?
I'm just saying, this "woman,"
I mean, she's fictitious, no?
- 왜 그런 말을 해요?
- 모니카 못 잊었잖아요
-Why would you say that?
-You're still into Monica.
You said there's somebody else
so she'd work with you.
딴 사람 있다고 해야
같이 일할 거고
오래 붙어있다 보면
마음이 움직일 거다...
If you spend time together,
maybe something might happen.
돗자리 깔아야겠네요
You're good. You're good.
No, I'm fairly intuitive. And psychic.
네, 전 직관력이
아주 뛰어나요
It's a substantial gift.
쓸만한 재능이죠
모니카한텐
비밀로 해주실래요?
Can you promise me
that you won't tell her?
Absolutely. I promise.
Tell her what?
그럼요, 약속해요
뭐라고 하겠어요?
Thanks a lot.
고마워요
아니, 정말이에요
기억력은 꽝이거든요
No, I'm serious.
I'm intuitive, but my memory sucks.
좋아
이번이 마지막이다
Okay, but this is the last time.
With a chick-chick here
And a chick-chick there
여기도 삐약
저기도 삐약
여기저기 삐약삐약
Here a chick, there a chick
Everywhere a chick-chick
삐약...
Chicken....
How's she doing?
우리 공주님은?
She?
공주님?
응, 여자 같지 않아?
Don't you think it's a she?
글쎄
I don't know.
순식간에 들어가 버려서
잘 모르겠어
I can't tell. Whatever it was
went back in too quickly.
I gotta change. I'm meeting
some of the cast for drinks.
옷 갈아입어야 돼
출연배우들하고 술 마셔
뭐야?
Excuse me?
왜?
What?
I stayed home while
you were at rehearsal...
지금까진 내가 '우리' 병아리랑
놀아줬으니까 이젠 네 차례야
...so somebody could be here
with our chick.
Who was up from 2:00 this
morning until 5:00...
새벽 2시부터 5시까지
안 자고 얘 재운 게 누군데?
...trying to get her back to sleep?
You don't think I get up
when you get up?
그 때 난 자고 있었냐?
Oh, here it comes.
- 또 시작이군
- 그래, 시작해보자
Yes! Here it comes!
I'm stuck here all day!
난 종일 붙어있는데
넌 우리랑 딱 2초 있다가
And then you come in
and spend two seconds with us...
친구랑 놀러나가겠다고?
...and then expect to go off
gallivanting with your friends?
Well, I don't think so, mister!
그건 안 되지, 아저씨
나도 좀 쉬어야지!
하루 종일 일했다구
I need to relax, okay?
I was working all day.
And you don't think
taking care of our chick is work?
'우리' 병아리 보는 건
일이 아닐까?
That's not what I said.
I just meant
누가 그렇대?
내 말은...
말 안 해도 알아!
I know what you meant!
Did you notice that ever since
we got this chick...
병아리 가져온 다음부터
훨씬 자주 싸우는 거 알아?
...we've been fighting
a lot more than we used to?
I don't know, maybe we weren't
ready to have a chick.
우린 병아리 키울
자격이 없나봐
내일 도로 갖다줄게
I'll take her back tomorrow.
We'll get our $3 back?
3달러는 안 돌려주겠지?
- 안녕
2시간 뒤에 방송이 있거든
좀 도와줘
I have that TV thing in two hours,
and I need your help.
What do you think?
This blue suit or this brown one?
곤색이랑 갈색 중에
어느 게 나아?
갈색은 눈매를, 곤색은
엉덩일 돋보이게 하더군
The brown one brings out your eyes.
But your butt looks great
in the blue one.
Really?
정말?
와! 아스피린 폭죽이네
That aspirin dance really works.
아직도 아픈 거야?
-ls that still...?
-I'm fine.
- 괜찮아
- 괜찮긴?
-No, you're not!
-Yes, I am.
- 괜찮대두
- 레이첼...
Look, I'm fine.
Watch. Look at that.
봐, 괜찮다니까
이것 봐
병원에 가봐야겠어
You've got to go to a doctor, okay?
사장님 댁에서
파티가 있어서 가봐야 돼
I have to get ready and go
to a dinner at my boss's house.
There's people there
that I have to meet.
정말 중요한 자리란 말야
사람들이 꽤나 반기겠다
I'm sure you'll make a great
impression. "Hi, I'm Rachel.
레이첼 그린이라고 해요
반갑습니다
It's nice to meet you."
Come on, you probably
have a broken rib.
갈비뼈 나갔으면 어쩌려고?
어차피 부러진 거라면
내일 가도 마찬가지야
I'll go to the hospital tomorrow.
It'll still be broken then.
- 준비나 도와주던가
- 레이첼...
But you know, I could use a hand
getting ready.
Either help me, or go.
안 도와줄 거면 가
Fine. I'll go.
좋아, 갈게
도와주고 가면 안 될까?
But before you go,
could you help me first?
알았어, 도와줄게
Sure. I'll help you.
비디오에 들어간 병아리
꺼내는 법 알아?
Good! Do you guys know how
to get a chick out of a VCR?
You know what?
I cannot do this with my left hand.
저기 있지...
왼손을 못 써서 그러는데
와서 좀 도와줄래?
Would you please help me
with this too?
- 이 브러쉬로 하지 뭐
- 그래
Let's use this brush.
- 이거야?
- 응, 조심해
-This stuff?
-Careful.
Light.
눈꺼풀을 쓸어내듯이 그려
쓸어내라구
Just sweep it across the lid.
Just sweep it.
Sorry!
- 미안
- 조심해
That's just poking me in the eye.
- 눈 찌를 뻔했잖아
- 미안해
I'm sorry. Close....
눈감아
-Just sweep it.
-I'm sweeping.
- 쓸어내리듯이...
- 알았어
그래
쓸어...
Sweep, sweep....
- 잘 펴 발라
- 왜?
Now make it even,
because we don't....
너무 진하지 않게
옅게 해
I don't want it to be too much.
I want it to be subtle.
아냐, 너무 옅게 칠하더라
You don't wear enough of this.
언제부터 너무 옅다고
생각했던 거야?
Since when do you think
I don't wear enough of this?
눈감아
더 예쁠 것 같단 말이야
Close your eye.
You're gonna like this better....
눈이나 감아
-Close, close.
-Blow it.
- 훅 불어
- 미안
이러니까 더 세련돼 보여
Because I think this will make you
a little more sophisticated.
밤일 나가는 여자처럼?
Sophisticated like a hooker?
- 안녕
- 왔어?
-Guess what I'm doing tonight.
-What?
- 오늘밤에 뭐하게?
- 뭔데?
피트랑 식당 구경가
I'm checking out
the restaurant with Pete.
- 모니카, 정말 잘 됐다
- 맞아
Monica, I am so excited for you!
- 너한테 할 말 있어
- 뭔데?
I have to tell you something.
What?
I can't tell you.
근데 말 못해
Wouldn't it be easier to tell
me something that you could tell me?
할 말 있으면 해버리는 게
속편하지 않을까?
그게 옳긴 하지
Well, sure, in a perfect world.
But no. I promised I wouldn't tell,
and I swore to all my Gods.
근데 말 안 하겠다고
굳게 맹세했거든
그래
Does it have to do with
Ross and Rachel?
- 로스랑 레이첼 문제야?
- 아니
Does it have to do with Joey?
- 그럼 조이 문제?
- 아냐
Does it have to do with Chandler
and that sock he keeps by his bed?
챈들러가 침대 맡에 놔두는
양말 얘기지?
아냐, 이따가
그 얘기나 해줘라
No, but let's come back to that later.
There you go!
Good enough for your party?
다 됐어
파티의 여왕이 되겠군
Sure.
정말!
Sure. I'll just sit next to
the transsexual from purchasing.
누가 보면 여장남자인 줄
알긴 하겠지만 말야
왜 그래?
자, 일어나
난 가볼게
All right, I gotta go,
So good luck at the party.
파티 잘 다녀와
Could you just stay
and help me get dressed?
옷 입는 것도
좀 도와줘
Sure.
그래, 좋아
Great. Okay, just turn around.
고마워
뒤돌아 서
What?
뭐?
I don't want you to see me naked.
벗은 거 보려고 그래?
새삼스럽게
왜 그러는 거야?
I've seen you naked a million times.
I ate hot fudge off you naked.
네 몸에 바른
핫퍼지도 먹었고
I sucked that mini-marshmallow
out of your bellybutton.
네 배꼽에서 마쉬맬로도
빼먹었다구
Yeah, but that was different.
We were going out then.
지금은 달라, 그 땐 우리가
사귈 때였지만 지금은 싫다구
Now it's weird.
레이첼, 지금도 원하면
언제든 볼 수 있어
Rach, you know, I can see
you naked anytime I want.
What?
뭐?
All I have to do is close my eyes.
See?
눈만 감으면 된다구
봐!
Ross, stop that!
- 하지 마
- 미안
나 두고 이젠
그런 생각하지 마
Come on! Don't think of me
like that anymore.
Sorry. Nothing you can do about it.
미안하지만 옛날 남자친구로서
그 정도 권리는 있다고 봐
It's one of my rights
as the ex-boyfriend.
어? 와!
Stop it! Cut it out! Cut it out!
그만 해!
하지 마!
미안해
다신 안 할...
I'm sorry. It will never happen
Wait a minute! Wait, wait....
잠깐 있어봐
네가 100명 있고
난 왕이야
Now there are 100 of you,
and I'm the king!
이상하게 생각할 것
없단 얘기야
Would you grow up? It's no big deal.
알았어
All right. Fine.
좋아
알았어!
안 되겠어
그냥 나 혼자 할게
See what you did?
I'm gonna be doing it by myself now.
Oh, my God. All right, look, look....
저런!
레이첼, 조심해
Easy. Easy.
You have to go to the hospital, okay?
- 병원 꼭 가봐, 알았지?
- 알았어, 꼭 갈게
I do. I really do.
코트 가져와서
택시 태워줄게
I'll get your coat,
then I'll put you in a cab.
같이 안 가줄 거야?
You're not gonna come with me?
Of course I am.
물론 가줘야지
I just have to make a call.
전화부터 하고
- 됐지?
- 고마워
Thank you.
왜 그래?
What's wrong?
이런 꼴로 병원에
갈 순 없잖아?
I'm sorry. I just can't go
to the hospital looking like this.
- 여행하고 관련 있어?
- 아니
Does it involve travel?
Does it involve clogs?
그럼... 밥통은?
잠깐!
밥통 아님 발톱?
Clogs or claws?
Clogs.
- 밥통
- 아냐
Claws?
- 그럼 발톱이야?
- 아니
So it doesn't involve Ross or Rachel
or Chandler or Joey.
로스랑 레이첼도 아니고
챈들러나 조이도 아니면
- 혹시 피트야?
- 아니!
What about Pete?
What is it?
뭔데?
무슨 얘긴데?
-What about Pete?
-I don't know!
몰라
답답해 환장하겠네
I feel like I'm talking to Lassie.
-Phoebe, would you just tell me?
-I can't!
- 빨리 말 안 해?
- 안 된다니까
- 가야겠어
- 거의 다 맞췄어
-I gotta go.
-But you're so close!
피트의 컴퓨터 회사랑
관련된 얘기지?
Something to do
with Pete's company?
그냥 가라
안 되겠다
Go! You'll never get it!
알아
I know.
그래, 야스민 블리스야
See, yes. That's Yasmine Bleeth.
She's a completely different
kind of chick.
너랑은 다른 종류의 영계지
I love you both.
둘 다 사랑한다구
But in very different ways.
종류는 생판 다른
사랑이지만...
- 나 왔어
- 어서 와
What are you doing?
You were gonna take her back.
어떻게 된 거야?
도로 갖다준다고 했잖아?
I did. But the store
wouldn't take her back.
안 받아주더라구
Then I took her to the shelter.
You know what I found out?
어쨌든 놀라운 사실을
알아냈어
If they can't find a home for her,
they kill her!
데려가는 사람이 없으면
죽여 버린대!
꼬마 야스민을
죽게 할 순 없었어
I won't let that happen
to little Jasmine.
그래, 잘했어
Good, good, because I was
kind of having second thoughts too.
안 그래도 좀 찜찜했어
그래, 병아리뿐 아니라
모든 동물이 마찬가지더라구
And it's not just chicks.
It's all kinds of other animals.
끔찍해라!
옳은 일을 한 거야
That's horrible.
You did the right thing.
그렇게 생각해주니 고마워
Thanks. I'm glad
you see it that way.
다 사연이 있지
Funny story!
I don't believe this!
꿈만 같아요!
냉장고 좀 보세요!
정말 크네요!
Look at this refrigerator!
It's gigantic!
들어가 살아도 되겠어요
좀 춥겠지만 하루이틀 일인가요?
I could live in this thing!
I'd be cold, but I'm always cold!
거미 프라이팬이네요!
정말 멋져요
Oh, my God! Look at these spider
burners! I love spider burners!
맘에 들어요?
So you like it?
맘에 들다마다요
It is so perfect!
Thank you so much.
- 너무 고마워요
- 뭘요
You're welcome.
Did you just smell my hair?
내 머리 냄새 맡았어요?
No! No way! What?
말도 안돼요
왜요? 아녜요
-Oh, God.
-What?
- 이런!
- 왜요?
아직 나 좋아하죠?
You still have feelings for me.
I'm just excited about the restaurant,
that's all.
아니에요, 식당 때문에
좋아서 그런 것뿐이에요
피트?
I love you. Is that so bad?
그래요, 사랑해요
그렇게 싫어요?
싫은 게 아니라...
절대 안 싫어요
No, it's not bad.
It's not bad at all.
It's really nice.
물론 기쁘지만...
The only one who stands to get hurt
is me, and I'm okay with that.
전 상처 같은 거
안 받으니까 괜찮아요
당신은 괜찮을지 몰라도
전 상처 주는 거 싫어요
You may be okay with getting hurt...
...but I am not okay with being
the one who hurts you.
That's why I can't take this job.
- 이 일 못하겠어요
- 뭐요?
What?
We probably shouldn't
see each other anymore.
이젠 안 만났음 좋겠어요
미안해요
I'm sorry.
괜찮아요
I mean, if that's
really what you want, okay.
당신이 정말 원한다면
괜찮다구요
잘 있어요
I'm sorry things
- 이렇게 헤어지게 돼서...
- 잠깐 입 다물고
Shut up for a second
and let me just see something.
가만 좀 있어 볼래요?
사실대로 말해 줘
You'd tell me the truth?
Rach, you can't look fat in an x-ray.
엑스레이에서 어떻게
뚱뚱하게 나와?
여기서 반성의 시간을
갖도록 해!
Now you stay out here
and you think about what you did!
- 얜 오리라구
- 불량 오리지!
-That's a duck!
-That's a bad duck!
How'd the thing go tonight, Ross?
오늘 잘 했어, 로스?
- 그게...
- 무슨 말이야?
What thing? What thing?
그냥 박물관 일이야
들어 가
Nothing. There was this thing
at the museum. Come on.
Easy.
조심하구
Now, when you come back, I hope you
remember that that chick is not a toy!
병아리는 네 장난감이
아니란 걸 깨닫기 바래
What "thing"? What is this "thing"?
무슨 일인지 말해 줘
오늘 '디스커버리 채널'에
나가기로 했었거든
I was kind of supposed to be on TV
tonight for the Discovery Channel.
Oh, my God!
세상에!
얘길 하지 그랬어?
Ross, why didn't you tell me that?
얘기했으면 가라고 했을 텐데
그럼 병원엔 누가 데려가?
I knew that if I told you,
you'd make me go...
...and I knew you needed someone
to be with you tonight. Come on.
가자
- 믿을 수가 없어
- 뭐가?
-I cannot believe you.
-What?
That is the sweetest thing.
너무 고맙긴 한데...
You should get some sleep.
- 가서 푹 자
- 알았어
- 그럼 난...
- 나 땜에 어떡해?
Sorry I spoiled your evening.
너만 안 아프면 됐어
As long as you're okay.
So I'll see you tomorrow.
그럼...
- 내일 봐
- 그래
See you.
잘 가
What did you do?
넌 뭐 잘못했냐?
What you doing?
뭐해?
Having a swim.
헤엄시키지
What about the chick?
병아리는?
Chicks don't swim.
병아린 헤엄 못 쳐
Are you sure?
확실해?
I don't know.
글쎄?
-Should we try?
-Sure.
- 시켜볼까?
- 좋지
See, I told you.
They don't swim.
내가 뭐랬어?
못 하잖아
Well, give him a minute.
- 좀 더 둬봐
- 안돼!
It's okay.
It's okay, baby, baby, baby.
이제 괜찮아
우리 아가